[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95_s04_01_SearchRing",
        "Type": "SeasonQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 61,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95_s04_01_SearchRing_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9501_Grace_s01_05",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95_s04_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "95A_Main_05",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95_s04_01_SearchRing_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
        "Title": "A Cold Welcome",
        "Description": "Skye is reporting news of unusual Varangian activity in Great Cleave. Go to investigate and put a stop to their plans.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What's going on?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Damned if I know! Seems our Spear Daughter wants your ear alone - as if the rest of us lot were untrustworthy. \\n\\nEh, maybe I'm in a mood. We should hear her out. Maybe check with her, find out what's going on?",
        "InProgressResponse": "Let me know what you find out. \\n\\nAnd remember, it's 'in business,' not 'in charity!'",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Mordred. Son of Morgaine! I've heard plenty about him, and none of it good. And now he's after some relics. \\n\\nSmells like desperate weather ahead. Ah, I don't like that look. You love this, don't you, working for free!",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95_s04_02_GetDaichi",
        "Type": "SeasonQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 61,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95_s04_02_GetDaichi_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9501_Grace_s01_05",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95_s04_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "95_s04_01",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95_s04_02_GetDaichi_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
        "Title": "Daichi Saito",
        "Description": "Grace O'Malley wants to add more firepower to the team. Find Daichi Saito and recruit him to the Silver Crows.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"-magical firepower?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Yeah, and literally, someone with magical fire. It’s a powerful element, I’m sure you’d agree.\\n\\nNothing better than fire to deal with those- what are they, Furious Trees. Or burn our way into a castle full of treasure.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Always good to bring more hands on deck, but our coffers are getting a bit dusty. Might need to trim our sails.\\n\\nHire some Ancient guardians- work long hours for a low wage. Relax, I’m joking. Do you think- nah.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Well, congratulations on hiring Daichi. He's no doubt a powerful add to the team. It's just-\\n\\nI wonder if you might have a word with him about that attitude of his. He won't listen to anything I say- calls me the \"lady with the hat.\"",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95_s04_03_EnterCastle",
        "Type": "SeasonQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 61,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95_s04_03_EnterCastle_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "95_s04_Grace_p01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95_s04_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "95_s04_02",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95_s04_03_EnterCastle_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
        "Title": "The Ice Castle",
        "Description": "Work with Daichi Saito to find a way into the legendary Ice Castle, and look for the Frost Crown.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"We can search the coast.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Good idea. Bound to find some small fishing or supply boats that way. I'll meet you on the island with the others. \\n\\nTruth is, I'm tired of paperwork. And I'm more than a bit curious to see Saito's wizardry.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Let’s keep an eye out for any interesting items in that Ice Castle. I’m certainly not hoping for any rewards from mad King Idris.\\n\\nBut the more we find out about Mordred, the more I agree with you- doing this for free.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "All things considered, a job well done. But make no mistake, we’re deep in the pickle brine now.\\n\\nWe mess this up, and there'll be an unwelcome visitor having a nice long stay with us. And its name is Winter.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95_s04_04_FightMage",
        "Type": "SeasonQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 61,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95_s04_04_FightMage_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9501_Grace_s01_05",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95_s04_04",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "95_s04_03",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95_s04_04_FightMage_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
        "Title": "The Mage",
        "Description": "Morgaine spoke of a mage who obtained the Staff of Samhain, the final artifact needed to empower Mordred and bring on an endless winter. Get the staff from the mage before Mordred does.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Let's split the team up.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Great idea. That way we've got a better chance of getting either the rune or the staff.\\n\\nWe know where the staff is- maybe you can take a team after that? The rest of us will look into the rune, figure out where it is.",
        "InProgressResponse": "We'll let you know what we find out about the Winter Rune. Ah, it might be time to start fortifying the camp.\\n\\nIf we get ahold of either the staff or the rune, there's nothing left for Mordred to do except come after us.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Cat's curse. Mordred's got everything he needs to turn us all into icicles, save the rune. We'll need to move fast.\\n\\nBrr. Is it just me, or did it get colder here, all of a sudden?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95_s04_05_RetrieveRune",
        "Type": "SeasonQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 61,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95_s04_05_RetrieveRune_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "95_s04_Daichi_p06",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95_s04_05",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "95_s04_04",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95_s04_05_RetrieveRune_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
        "Title": "The Winter Rune",
        "Description": "Get the Winter Rune that binds the three winter artifacts together, before Mordred gets to it.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Great Cleave.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Great Cleave- what? Don't tell me you just guessed that. All right, don't make a display of yourself.\\n\\nAt first I thought the map you got from Mordred might be for the Winter Rune, but there are no waterfalls by the Forge.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Just when things were getting quiet again. I knew I couldn't trust it. Why can't we have a nice, fat, boring, purse-fattening contract? \\n\\nEscort a rich old lady across the street. Find a lost, priceless jewel.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "This Mordred- he does not know it, but something cold, hungry, a terror- it breaks free of its tether, in a place that shadows our world. \\n\\nWe must stop him. The weakness of humanity- it will bring ruin on us all.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95_s04_06_StopDevice",
        "Type": "SeasonQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 61,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95_s04_06_StopDevice_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9501_Grace_s01_05",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95_s04_06",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "95_s04_05",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95_s04_06_StopDevice_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
        "Title": "Eternal Frost",
        "Description": "Mordred has everything he needs to activate the Ancient device and become a winter demigod. Stop him before he brings about an Ice Age to Aeternum, and the rest of the world.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"The map is Mokosh Springs?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I thought everyone already knew this. The waterfalls, the mountain shape- Mokosh.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Skye may know a way to find Morgaine. You know, I like Skye very much. \\n\\nShe always says exactly what she thinks. What? No, I do not care for her in that way. She is- skinny like a chicken, and not enough hair.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "If we were betting odds, I might have wagered against us. \\n\\nBut you and I together, we've got a kind of magic all our own, don't we? We bested that smug arse Mordred.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95_s04_07_WrapFrost",
        "Type": "SeasonQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 61,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95_s04_07_WrapFrost_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95_s04_07",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "95_s04_06",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95_s04_07_WrapFrost_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
        "Title": "From Client to Crow",
        "Description": "Mordred has been stopped, and another crisis averted, for now. Share the news with his mother, Morgaine.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Let's pay her a visit.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I was hoping you'd say so. Skye just came back, says she tried approaching her, but the sorceress had her jaw set.\\n\\nDetermined to stay out of things. Maybe catch up with Skye. I'll join you out there.",
        "InProgressResponse": "To think this entire place, maybe the whole world, would be covered in ice, if it wasn't for the Silver Crows. \\n\\nWhat do you mean, mostly thanks to you? Ah, you’re having me on again, aren't you?",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Seems I just missed it. How did the talk with Morgaine go? Wonder if we could still ask her for some eh, reasonable compensation.\\n\\nJust enough to cover our expenses. Not to mention having to put up with that son of hers.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "S04_GT_EXPD_01",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 61,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "S04_GT_EXPD_01_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9504_Shailyn_s04_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "s04_GT_EXPD_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "95_s01_X1",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "S04_GT_EXPD_01_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": null,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
        "Title": "The Glacial Tarn (Expedition)",
        "Description": "Shailyn has found another way into the underground caverns in Great Cleave. She wants you to pursue Ser Loth and destroy him.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Ser Loth is here?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Yes, right through this gateway, in fact. But as you can imagine, there's more in the way of getting to Loth than just this door. \\n\\nNot only his allies, the Varangians, but powerful magic. Primordial. And most deadly.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Though the challenge before us is mighty, I can think of none more able to face it, than you.\\n\\nThe way you handled our foes at the Empyrean Forge- it was- impressive, young one.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You've done it. You've actually, actually done it. Forgive me. I- I have spent a lifetime, pursuing that vile bastard, Loth.\\n\\nI am in your debt. More than you know. And at last, there shall be rest.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "S04_GT_EXPD_RPT",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 61,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "S04_GT_EXPD_RPT_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "95_s04_AoWei",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "S04_GT_EXPD_RPT_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "DarkMatter",
        "ItemRewardQty": 5,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": 1,
        "CanBeAbandoned": "TRUE",
        "Title": "The Ice of Life (Expedition)",
        "Description": "The healer Ao Wei, is interested in the potential for curative powers of ice found in the Glacial Tarn in Great Cleave. He wants you to collect samples of any interesting ice formations that you find deep in the caverns.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"You want me to gather ice?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "That is correct! But this ice- it has properties unlike anything I have ever seen. Is it the purity of the water?\\n\\nThe magical essence it soaks in? I must have more samples to study! Please, will you help me?",
        "InProgressResponse": "Beyond its healing properties, I believe these ice formations hold a secret to our life here on Aeternum.\\n\\nI know I am barely scratching the surface of these mysteries but they must be uncovered!",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Ah! I see you have returned! And you have the ice formations! Excellent! I knew you were the right person to ask for aid!\\n\\nIf ever you are in need of healing, seek me out! I shall return this favor to you then, I assure you!",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    }
]
